Hey, Omi?
Mm-ya?
What we saw earlier... Whaddaya think it was?
Could be some kind of Right.
You lose your Rights when you die,
so someone else beside the
Emperor might be behind it.
I thought so, too.
Sane and Saaya's bodies
were perfectly preserved,
and the Emperor's body was gone entirely.
But who would do that? And why?
Good work, you two.
Sensei! I thought you were on watch duty.
I had someone fill in for me.
There's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
About what?
It's about Raion...
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
I see.
So you failed in exterminating them
and ran back home.
My sincerest apologies...
No matter.
At least we've gained some useful information
about the Prime Right of Materialization.
You're forgiven. However...
Showing them your Water Utilization
was a mistake.
They'll have a strategy to kill you next time.
If you don't want to die, come with me.
I'll perform a ritual on you.
But in return...
Swear your eternal loyalty
to me. Over and over.
About Raion?
What's up?
He's certainly reliable, but he's also
easily swayed by his emotions.
I'm not sure it's wise to put him
in charge of strategies by himself.
That was never the plan.
Besides, we don't want him
to take the fall like Saneatsu.
Well, he's definitely quick on his feet,
so maybe we can just throw him
into the line of fire!
You're heartless.
It's not ideal to be without a strategist,
but we'll all just have to work together.
Oh, almighty Queen, ruler
of the heavens and earth.
Grant this powerless fool your
great love and benevolence.
Oh, almighty Queen, ruler
of the heavens and earth.
Grant this powerless fool your
great love and benevolence.
Oh, almighty Queen, ruler
of the heavens and earth...
There's a missing officer candidate,
Yoshiaki Hirayama.
And another missing experiment
member, Hikari Ebina.
Since when?
Attendance records show that both
had returned as scheduled.
But according to other members, Hikari
Ebina hasn't been back in over a month.
Who recorded attendance?
Hirayama, given that he was the most
promising of the candidates...
Terminate all candidates
except the top three.
As you wish.
That saves us some hassle.
As for you...
Starting today, you'll have
the Prime Right of Electricity.
Thank you, my Queen...
Individuals can only possess one
Prime Right and Right each....
Once obtained, they can't be replaced.
But the Queen's powers flips
that principle on its head.
The first of Lady Kisaragi's
powers is total control
over the selection and obtainment of Rights!
As long as we serve Lady Kisaragi,
we'll always have the upper hand!
Ikusa, you'll be given more tasks
in the area of housing.
I trust you'll work hard.
Housing?! For what, milady?!
Lady Kisaragi, I've brought you
the candidates.
Touya Mutsuki, Knight Kato, and Lili Kato.
These are the top three officer candidates.
Starting today, you three will be
sent to the front lines to fight.
Don't disappoint me, Team Frontline.
Yes, milady.
Cool. Thanks, hag!
Cut it out, Knight!
Are you sure about this, Lady Kisaragi?
Ikusa prefers to be on the battlefield.
I don't believe he'll be happy...
We must avoid informing the current
Emperor of his new Prime Right.
He'll be used when the time is right.
How I look forward to
the day of our victory...
At this pace, it shouldn't be much longer.
What should I do first?
Tell me... Emperor.
We got some great stuff today!
Nothing beats hunting down
survivors to steal food!
Take a look, Yocchin!
I bet there's double yesterday's amount!
The Emperors
Wow! We've been so lucky ever
since Yohei became the leader!
It may not be long before we
conquer this land as The Emperors...
Standing up to the Emperor!
You're so cool, Yocchin!
This pungent, foul stench,
and these piercing, vulgar voices...
Who the hell are you?!
I'm the Cleaner.
I exterminate civil waste for the Queen
who will lead us into the ideal world.
You'll be deleted.
W-what's going on?!
My body's so heavy...
What the hell did you do?!
Get crushed, penetrate the earth,
and enrich the soil.
It's so heavy...
I-I'm gonna be crushed...
Damn!
Yohei! What did you do?!
I dunno what you did,
but I'm not willing to die!
This man... How is he moving?
Die!
Piss off!
It rebounded!
He must have some kind of Prime Right.
All the more reason
to exterminate him here and now.
I won't let anyone
get in Lady Kisaragi's way.
Are you reinforcement?
You... mentioned something about a Queen?
I hope I'm not mistaken.
I'm just excited to get more information.
I'll delete anyone who stands in the way.
Get crushed, penetrate the earth, and...
Enrich the soil!
Hmm, I think I've got a good grasp
of your Prime Right.
My Prime Right...
The ability to control gravity
within a 10-meter radius.
Gravity Right
The Prime Right of Gravity.
Right now, he's standing in
gravity 50 times the usual force.
Assuming he's about 60 kilograms,
that would total a weight of 3 tons...
And why are the glass shards floating?
I'll make it 100 times the usual force then!
If that doesn't work...
A thousand times!
It's no use.
Did your Prime Right come
with the definition of gravity?
I knew it! He has a Prime Right too...
No matter! Crush him!
A thousand times the force!
General relativity states that gravity is
the result of distortions in time-space.
Were you aware of that?
It's not working!
Does his Prime Right neutralize
the power of others?!
Perhaps it could be described as the energy
that drains into these distortions.
Which would make countering them very easy.
Simply maneuver the direction
of energy to stop the force.
As a result, gravity doesn't change one bit.
This was a bad match-up for you.
Get off your high horse...
...and die!
How's that!
Oh, my. Good for you.
He flung back the ceiling I dropped on him?!
How is he alive?!
Right behind you.
Why, you! Who are you?!
Listen, why don't we have a seat?
Let's have a nice chat after we capture you.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
More reinforcements?! But when?
How could he have—
Don't tell me...
That split second...
he was hiding among the rubble?
So he was waiting for that moment all along?!
How could he make such
a split-second decision?
Or was it predetermined?
But wait—that would mean...
They read my moves?!
You mean he knew I would drop the ceiling
on him before he even appeared?!
Your call, Pres.
You sure you want me to do it?
Sure, go ahead. I'll adjust it accordingly.
Prime Right of...
Explosion Right
Explosion!
I used my Prime Right of Induction
to lead the blast the other way.
Hey, you're right!
This way, there's no damage to me!
You're amazing, Pres!
I think you'll eventually be able to
do it yourself with some practice.
But, man, how did you know he'd
drop the ceiling on you beforehand?
It's nothing complicated.
If gravity itself won't work, there's
no choice but to use another method of attack.
Gravity works from the top down, so
dropping the ceiling is just the ticket.
Okay, but like... is he alive?
He's alive. A few moments ago...
I set my Suspension Right
so it would activate
when he felt his life was
in danger and halt time.
Oh yeah!
That's why you let him attack you!
Coincidence or not, we're lucky
to capture a suspect.
Now, shall we head home?
But how will we carry him?
Gravity is always at work.
My Induction Right can
control anything, anytime.
Man... You're like a cheater, Pres.
That was cutting it close...
Without this Prime Right,
the Right of Transference,
Transference Right
I'd be dead by now.
And I used those guys as scapegoats...
...by transferring them all the damage.
This always happens.
I always let go of the things
most important to me.
I swore to stick by them
until the end... but still, I...
I'm the Cleaner.
I exterminate civil waste for the Queen
who will lead us into the ideal world.
The Queen... She's that bastard's boss!
Demoted?!
Yup!
We're not sure you're cut out for it, so
you're demoted to Assistant Strategist!
Isn't that a bit too straightforward?
But there's no Head Strategist,
so things will be decided by vote?
Okay, but...
I'm playing my trap card!
No, wait! I take it back!
They seem way too comfortable...
In times like these,
it's best to let loose a little.
Let's gather around for
today's strategy meeting.
So we don't have any clue
as to the Queen's whereabouts...
If you're not dead set on
organizing a preemptive attack,
we could just wait for their first move
and prepare in the meantime.
I vote nay to that!
Hard to prepare for anything
when we don't even know
the first thing about their abilities.
Mm-yup, we'd need to know
what Rights they have...
Support
Defense
Offense
Our primary offense is Ryuta, and
Omi and Rika are our main defense.
Eren, Nishime, and I can act as support.
Death
Souma's an all-rounder, but he can
only materialize three times a day tops.
So we're still a defense-heavy unit overall...
You're right. We don't have much
of a chance without a striker.
Hey... this is a shot in the dark, but...
Why don't we try recruiting Ren Iruga?
If he joins us, that's another striker
and we'll have better chances of winning.
Ren Iruga?
He was originally our enemy.
I think he had a change of heart
in the end, but...
We have no clue where he went
after defeating the Emperor.
If he still has Gobo's communication device,
we should be able to call him in.
Is he any good?
Of everyone we've seen... he's the strongest.
So that settles that.
Could you send him a message?
We already have, multiple times.
I doubt it'll work, for real.
Not that I won't try, but...
The Queen could already be on the move
while we're talking like this.
I'm sure they'll try to trace our footsteps.
But we haven't left any,
so they won't have any leads.
The question is... what to do then?
Of course! That'll be our play!
Ya come up with an idea?
Yeah. We'll have to be assertive
if we want to edge out the Queen!
So I'll lie!
What did you just say?
Touya Mutsuki is missing?
He left this morning to investigate,
but it's past his scheduled return
and he's nowhere to be found.
I see. You can stand back.
Yes, milady.
What do you think, Lady Kisaragi?
Someone working for the
current Emperor defeated him.
It's safe to assume that's what happened.
We should act on the premise that they
now know everything Mutsuki knows...
Yes, perhaps we should leave here at once.
Outside, Knight Kato will be the front guard.
Meguru will be the rear guard.
And inside, Lili Kato will be the front guard.
And Ikusa will be the rear guard.
I'll take Kou as my personal bodyguard,
and observe from afar.
You impostor... I swear to you...
I'll kill you!
Lady Kisaragi, it's time for
the Emperor's announcement.
There's only so much they can do
with mere text announcements.
The current Emperor's influence
won't grow any greater.
I suppose I can check if they try
to probe us for any information...
What could that be?
I-It can't be!
Citizens across Japan, good evening.
This is your Emperor.
We will be commencing
Stage Three of Tasuketsu.
National Instant Alert System
The National Instant
Alert System... JP-Alert!
Of course!
They used the Materialization
Right for equipment!
There's only one rule to Stage Three:
Capture the Queen who's hiding.
We will commence tomorrow at 10:00 AM.
Once someone succeeds,
all other participants will die as the
majority being "unsuccessful participants".
They used Stage Two of the real Tasuketsu
to their advantage and avoid any suspicion...
Dammit! At this rate...
So they put you at the center
of Tasuketsu itself...
Participants will assume
it's another game development
if you make an announcement yourself.
This will revive the Emperor's influence!
No, something isn't right...
This would unquestionably set off
a killing spree among fools
who can't distinguish between
myself and other participants...
I highly doubt the current Emperor
would do such a thing.
This is all a façade?
Yes. And given the chance that they
have knowledge of our location,
this may be the current
Emperor's first move to kill me.
Either way, I believe it's best we relocate.
Yes, and we must gather information
on them as soon as possible.
That was maybe your biggest lie yet, Raion.
This way, we can make sure
the Emperor still has authority.
But now what?
Won't survivors start
killing each other to find—
Nah, you'll see.
I don't expect the general public
to be able to find the Queen.
The Queen should know that much, too.
I'm sure they want dirt on us, so hopefully
they make a move one way or another.
You sure we can act based on assumption?
Well yeah, we have no information to go off.
If we guess right, then awesome.
They're in the same boat as us...
which is exactly why I instigated first.
I hope they'll come searching for
anywhere with the slightest chance.
Like KHN?
But... wouldn't they already
have been there by now?
There's one place I'm betting on.
I'll tell you the details later,
but I'm hoping we can come in contact
with the Queen's troops there.
That place is...
So, why bet on the Emperor's tower?
They've already figured out that
the current Emperor's a fake, right?
Then what would they assume
about the original Emperor?
Umm... they've been captured, they've
died, or just somehow disappeared?
Yeah, so when?
Naturally, they'd assume something
happened when Tasuketsu ended,
and announcements changed from
voice-overs to text announcements.
So, that part's obvious.
The only other question is how much
the Queen knows about the Emperor's tower.
The effects of the Concealment Right
have worn off,
and the tower is visible to anyone now.
It wouldn't surprise me if
the Queen came to see it herself.
There's a chance she took
the Emperor's body, too!
Yeah, and another thing.
One look inside and it's obvious
there was a battle there.
So whoever fought the Emperor...
...would likely be the current Emperor.
The tower is the only place the "real" Emperor
came in contact with the "fake" Emperor.
And that makes it the best, and likely
only, place to gather any information.
I get it now!
So that's why you instigated!
Get down!
Man... this is such a drag
first thing in the morning.
What a brat! Stop complaining
and get to work, Knight!
The Lie
That's them!